IN LOVING MEMORY OF MOTHER
The hemorrhage was severe.
-She has lost a lot of blood--
-Is my wife alive or not?
Sorry, we couldn't save her.
But your son is safe and healthy.
Jay, my son.
Music is a drug.
They say…
"Those with the gift of
music and rhythm…
have been touched by God."
But that's a lie.
Do you know
why those crazy people
like performing on stage?
Because they get
addicted to the applause.
This applause eventually
intoxicates their veins and nerves.
Their addiction to one drug
leads to another.
Little by little, music will
take away everything from you.
Among all the diseases
and among all the addictions,
the worst of all is… music!
This is Jay.
My Jay!
He is a singer and song writer.
He sings for me.
And he's deeply in love with me.
I'm Sophia.
Today is my big day.
My annual charity show's
big finale is about to start.
You are making this, right?
Harry!
-Harry!
-The plan is very simple.
Dancers will exit from the left.
The lights will be off.
-Our winning designer--
-Sophia Singhania.
Sophia Singhania.
She'll go on stage and give a speech.
Sophie will give a speech?
Yes. She's the winner after all.
-She can't speak.
-What do you mean?
She's mute.
There's no need for a speech.
Her work does the talking.
Come on, guys!
Everybody, get ready!
-Three minutes! I want everyone on stage!
-Presenting on stage, Sophia Singhania!
Ladies and gentlemen, give it up!
What can I say, Sophia?
I was shattered into a thousand fragments
You held me in a warm embrace, Sophia
And now, I've become whole again
You're the fire that brings warmth
Your love is all I need
To drive out all the darkness
You burn bright as a lamp
In your silence, Sophia
I listen to my mother tongue
Your eyes tell me stories, Sophia
You bring me solace
Hold it correctly, man!
Hey, Jay! What's up?
-How many do you want?
-Two.
This whole world was
created for you, Sophia.
Just for you.
When our fingers are intertwined, Sophia
I feel like I have
The world in the palm of my hand
When we lock lips, Sophia
I feel like the skies are at my feet
Sophia!
Sophia…
Oh! Deep within me!
Check, check!
And what's this? Oh!
Yeah! Who is your daddy?
Who is your daddy?
Love it!
-Sanju Singhania.
-I'm Jay.
It's an honor, sir.
Sophie's Jay.
Finally, we meet!
Please have a seat.
If I knew you had so much fun here,
I'd skip work every day
and come here instead.
-Anytime, sir.
-I mean, does all this gear
belong to you?
There's a secret behind that.
Tell me more.
-Dandiya.
-No!
Throughout the year, we play
at festivals and weddings.
We buy the gear by
performing at various events.
Amazing!
-Have you completed your graduation?
-Yes, a few years ago.
I'm doing my Masters now.
-What's your major?
-Music Technology.
Technology!
It looks like you're into it.
Music.
-Sir, sorry to disturb you.
-Yeah?
There are four
missed calls from Mr. Parekh.
-I gotta take this call.
-Sir.
-We gotta hang. You and me.
-Thank you, sir.
-We gotta spend some alone time.
-Thanks.
Give me that phone.
Parekh! I love you, baby.
You know I love you.
Bro, listen up!
That's G-Medal, right?
Hey, Sophie! This is for you.
The winning band is going to get
the headline slot at graduation.
There are no auditions.
-We just have to upload a song.
-What song?
-Don't you have one?
-But which song?
You write many songs.
Just send one of those.
I don't have song that will
help us win this competition.
Just send any song!
I know we'll be selected.
You get one decent song
after writing a hundred songs.
And you probably have a thousand songs!
-It's our time to shine.
-Ball, please!
Hey, chinki!
Could you please pass the ball?
-Thank you, sahebji.
-Listen…
-Yeah!
-Ignore them.
It's our graduation.
We must perform on stage together.
It'll be our first time.
I don't know, man!
We may not get another chance…
-Hey, Jackie Chan!
-Bro!
Chop Suey!
Hey, Changi!
Thank you!
Thank you, Changi!
-What…
-Hey, Jay!
Listen to me. You have that
old album with you, right?
The first two tracks
in that album are really good.
We'll send that first.
We have got to do this.
Listen to me, Jay. Ignore them!
Please let go.
Hey! Jay, stop it!
Jay, what are you doing? Stop it!
Damn you!
Thanks for that, man.
Anything for you, dude.
Well, then, send the song.
Which song?
The song you sang yesterday. It was cool.
That won't help us win.
This is where we've talked and laughed
Right here
We leaned on our friend's shoulder
Tomorrow may be uncertain
But we don't dwell on sadness
Music is the voice of friendship
It'll be in our memories forever
There's no other place like this
It teaches us the way of life
It gives us wings to fly
I would never want this dream to end
Next up, The Momos!
Oh, tomorrow!
Hey, tomorrow!
The sun will shine brighter tomorrow
The future is ours
This is just the beginning of a journey
Our names will be etched in these walls
There will be stories
Behind every scribbling
We just want our friends by our side
For this is the only time
We truly live our lives
Oh, tomorrow!
Hey, tomorrow!
The sun will shine brighter tomorrow
The future is ours
This is just the beginning of a journey
There's love among us
There's anger among us
But our bond is beyond
Everything in this world
There's love among us
There's anger among us
But our bond is beyond
Everything in this world
Are you ready to sing out loud?
-Our first love
-We'll never forget!
-All our girlfriends
-This beautiful day
-We'll never forget!
-The late night dance sessions
-What about the library?
-We'll never forget!
-What about the canteen?
-All the classes we bunked
-We'll never forget!
-All these beautiful memories
My father was right.
There's no drug like applause.
Say that after you try other drugs.
You're a rock star, man!
-Let's take a photo. Where's your family?
-Well…
-Hey…
-Right here.
Come on. Let's do this.
Mr. Singhania, please smile!
Oh, man!
I had no idea that
you're such a rock star!
I love it. I'm blown away.
This weekend…
I have some people coming over.
I want you to be there.
You'll be my guest of honor.
You'll be the man of the moment.
We'll party!
She's waiting for you. Go on.
Get out of here!
Hey, tomorrow!
The sun will shine brighter tomorrow
The future is ours
This is just the beginning of a journey
Your story always seemed strange to me.
There's no need for that.
You could have died last night.
You know that, right?
I don't know why, but I had
a feeling that I should keep this safely.
Your story is very interesting.
To me, you're an angel in disguise
You have captivated me
You have taught me the language
Of music through your eyes
The moment I saw you
I knew I was yours
Mr. Singhania's daughter's
performance is beautiful!
Both the performances are beautiful.
Your painting and my music
Have been intertwined
Our world is a land
Of a thousand rainbows
It's a song
That is heard by none
I now see things through your eyes
Your eyes are full of language
It is the language of my music
Your visage is as beautiful
As a blooming lotus
You are the reason for my smile
You are the reason
For my smile
If this continues,
you can make a lot of money.
Actually… no!
More than the one
who makes the music,
the one who brings it
to the market earns more.
Do I have to tell you this?
Let me give you an example.
He sings a song,
and we will buy that.
-We'll release it under his name…
-Jay!
-and make money out of it.
-Come here for a second.
Let's put it this way.
I would like you to meet the Honorable
Chief Minister, Mr. Prabhakar.
I would like to call you a friend.
He's very keen to get to know you.
Nice to meet you, sir.
The song you just performed
started with a fugue…
right?
Oh! So, you know about it.
I started the…
Classical Music Appreciation Club
at Delhi University.
I especially like JS Bach's fugues…
that have feeling.
I'm glad you liked my song, sir.
When did I say I liked it?
Music either reflects
reality or it doesn't.
Your music is good.
It will also reflect reality someday.
-Good luck!
-Thank you, sir.
-A drink?
-No, sir.
A rock star who doesn't drink!
You're really one of a kind.
Cheers!
So…
You love Sophie?
Very much, sir.
What are you willing to do for your love?
Sophia and I wish to get married.
How easy it is for the unmarried
to say that they want to get married!
That's a waste of time!
-Do you doubt my intentions--
-No. I don't doubt you.
Sophie must have chosen you
because she saw something in you.
She may be unable to speak,
but she understands everything.
She knows why I asked you to come here.
Jay…
I want to give India
a new means of listening to music.
I want to start an AI streaming service.
It's a brand new technology…
that goes into your phone, into
your tablet, into your computer…
and into your mind.
But I need someone to lead this.
I want you to do it.
Together, we will make it happen.
I'm totally convinced…
that I want you.
It would be an honor, sir.
-But…
-You're practically family.
Come on!
Whom else am I going to ask?
Sir, with all due respect…
I want to do something else.
What do you want to do?
-Music.
-Hey, I'm also talking about music.
But I don't look at music as a business.
It's all music.
It's all connected with music.
I want to be a musician, sir.
I want to write my own lyrics,
compose music and perform.
How will you make a living?
What do you mean, sir?
Sophie and I have lot of dreams, sir.
We wish to travel the world
for a few years.
I want to write songs
and perform live gigs.
Sophie can explore her passion,
which is art and dance.
We just want to travel for a while.
Explore ourselves. Find ourselves.
There's something between us, sir.
Oh… it's magic!
-You feel like it's magic!
-It's something magical.
It's… like a poem.
You'll walk into the sunset.
Hand in hand.
Come on!
Look around you.
Look where you're sitting right now.
I have toiled to get to this position.
And I have raised Sophie with great care.
Why should I permit some struggling
artist to marry my daughter?
I promise you, sir.
I'll always keep her happy.
How?
Will you perform
at a dandiya event?
Do you ave any idea
how much the families of artists
have to struggle,
in the name of art?
All in the name of art!
Because you artists can only
love yourselves.
Sir, I believe…
music can change lives.
Just one song…
can change the whole world.
One song can change the world!
And… drum roll!
You have that song!
You have composed that song.
I'm in the presence…
of true art.
Let me hear it.
Come on, let me hear it.
Hit me, come on!
I want to hear it.
Where is the song?
I'm all ears, son. I'm all ears.
Do you have a song like that?
I'll tell you.
You want to become a musician.
So, compose good music first.
Why just one song?
Compose a hundred songs.
And then, we'll see…
whether your song can
change the world or not.
Until then, don't even think
about meeting or talking to Sophie.
That's my offer.
Do you love Sophie deeply enough?
A hundred songs!
I have raised Sophie with great care.
Why should I permit some struggling
artist to marry my daughter?
Because you artists can only
love yourselves.
Where is the song?
You have composed that song.
One song can change the world!
Do you have a song like that?
Where is the song?
Until then, don't even think
about meeting or talking to Sophie.
Music has ruined our family.
Why just one song?
Compose a hundred songs.
Go inside and choose
your birthday present.
Go on.
Where did you find this, son?
Prepare the bill.
Hey, where did you find this?
You've made a good choice, boy.
-We don't want that.
-Buy it. The strings are free.
Two hundred and eighty-seven…
We don't want it.
Sir, it's not for you. The boy
wants it. It's a child's guitar.
I said, we don't want it!
Hey!
Selling this guitar won't pay my bills.
We're insisting because the boy likes it.
We'll give you a 20% discount. That's it!
He talks just like my father.
You love Sophie, don't you?
Why don't you just elope with her?
Why do you need his permission?
No, that will be wrong.
It's the 21st century, man!
Maybe, even 22nd!
I won't do that.
That means
you're going to write the songs!
A hundred songs!
If that's your final decision…
then come with me.
Where?
Shillong, bro.
The best place on earth.
Especially to write songs.
You were made for Shillong.
We'll record a hundred songs
and throw them in his face.
What do you say?
I've hidden a tune
for you in this tiny box.
Whenever you hear it,
you will know…
that there's music within me.
And that music…
is you, Sophie.
Don't ask why I am going away.
But I will come back for you…
and take you away.
And if I fail to do that…
then, maybe, I'm unworthy of you.
My life without you
Is like a flowerless garden
Why should I live without you?
Oh, my love!
My life without you
Is like a flowerless garden
Why should I live without you?
Answer me, my love
Oh, my love!
You are the essence of all my songs
You are my only desire
My longing is for you, only you
Without you, I am nothing
I'm a lone bird in the sky
I'm yearning for your presence
Without you, my wings are clipped
There are only tears in my eyes
You are my muse
Without you
There's a storm inside of me so intense
You are my muse
Without you
There's a storm inside of me so intense
My life without you
Is like a flowerless garden
Why should I live without you?
Answer me, my love
Oh, my love!
All my dreams, all my desires
Begin and end with you
Now that you're not in my sight
My world has lost its daylight
I have a longing for peace
I'm alone in the wilderness
Emily!
Esther!
Uncle Kong!
Grandma!
Is it Sunday today?
Hey!
Hey, my hair!
Okay!
What is this? Dad, look.
My sister Pauline has come back!
How are you, son?
Christopher, Daphne, Emily, Esther.
Emilia and my Pops.
This is the weirdo.
And this is the queen of
our house, our Grandma!
-God bless you.
-Hi!
-This is my cute mother.
-Hello.
She's the source of all
the cuteness in the world.
-Hello.
And this is Humpy.
Humpy? Why Humpy?
You'll find out soon.
That's Uncle Kong.
-Hello.
-Uncle Kong has seven kids.
Sa, Re, Ga, Ma, Pa, Da, Ne.
One is on the way.
They're aiming for an octave!
Yeah!
This is my family.
By the way, guys, this is Jay.
-Amen.
-Tell us that story.
-I have an embarrassing story of Polo.
Hey, shut up! Not right now.
What is that? Jimi?
On T-shirt its written Jimi, Jimi.
-Hendrix?
-Is there another Jimi?
Do you know Hendrix?
Who doesn't know Hendrix?
Fine. Sing me a Hendrix song.
-Yeah.
-Which song do you know?
Who doesn't know Jimi Hendrix!
Tell me.
Was he a left-handed guitarist
or a right-handed guitarist?
Left-handed or right-handed?
All guitarists are righties!
Everyone except you knows that.
Look, wearing a Jimi Hendrix T-shirt
-doesn't make you Jimi Hendrix.
-Pappu.
I understand.
I know, dad.
That's why I became a drummer.
Right, Popo?
Why didn't you tell me?
What?
About your family…
and your home.
This is insane, bro!
They're all musicians.
Of course, they're insane.
You're just like them!
I know.
You're very lucky.
Humpy!
Well, I'm off to bed.
You know your room, right?
Hey, Polo!
Thanks, buddy.
He is thanking me!
Why just one song?
Compose a hundred songs.
As time passed…
Jay began composing songs.
And slowly…
Shillong grew on him.
And with each passing day,
with each song,
we were getting closer
to being together.
But then, all of a sudden,
his inspiration dried up.
A change was needed.
-Let's go.
-Where?
Where are you taking me? Hey!
Red Mascara. It's one of the
finest jazz clubs in the country, man.
There are auditions going on inside.
You might get your inspiration here.
-Pearl Masters, bro.
-Polo!
-Chandi.
-Hey!
-Nice to meet you.
-I'm glad. Nice to meet you.
-You are…
-Jay.
-Jay, welcome to Shillong, bro.
-Thank you.
Bijoy!
The drummer and the pianist.
-Oh, you are the Mumbai boys!
-Hi!
You guys are good.
But whether you are good enough or not
is for her to decide.
It all depends on your performance.
Good luck, guys!
Hello?
Let's do this!
Ladies and gentlemen,
give it up for Sheila,
the jazz queen of Shillong!
Let me tell you a story
A mad, fleeting love story
Can you tell me
How it will end?
You once promised me
That you would lay your head on my lap
And breathe your last
But today…
You are here with another woman
I say, it's foolishness
It is now time
To measure your love
Do you really love me?
Tell me
Don't you lie to me
Or I will burn you alive!
How deep is your love?
Do you really love me?
Don't you lie
Or a bullet will pierce your heart
A bullet will pierce your heart
Tell me, do you love me?
Where did all your love go, my friend?
What about all the promises you made?
Tonight, you are here, my friend!
But where did all your love go?
Were those hugs and kisses
Not enough, my friend?
Tonight, there will be a shower of bullets
And not kisses!
So, tell me!
Out with it!
If you lie
A bullet will pierce your heart
Where did all your love go, my friend?
What about all the promises you made?
Tonight, you are here, my friend!
Where did all your love go, my friend?
That was good, right?
Hey, pianist!
She wants to see you.
-Do you have a cell phone?
-I do.
Put it on silent mode.
My phone is on silent mode.
So?
Won't she call me next?
Oh, God!
These kids, man!
So, you're the one in
search of a hundred songs!
-How do you know about that?
-Sit.
Everyone in Shillong knows about that.
Drink?
No, thank you. I don't drink.
And thank you for letting me
play as a part of your band.
-Why are you still here?
-I'm waiting for him.
Go home.
He'll be out only after
writing a hundred songs.
Do you play classical music?
For those who don't
know much about it, yes.
But I've never had the guts to play
for those who know classical music.
Jay, classical music is for people…
who like rules.
Jazz is for the living.
The fearless.
Do you want to be a composer?
Yes.
From where did you learn music?
Hey, Farukh!
Where the hell are you?
Timing is the mark of a good piano tuner.
Hey, come here!
Your father forbade you
from coming here, right?
Shall I call him now?
Did you forget what
happened the other day?
But I've come here as a customer.
Customer?
What do you want to buy?
How many music lessons
do you give per month?
Five lessons in a month.
How long is each lesson?
An hour long.
-What is this for?
-Fees for five minutes of a lesson.
Please ask him to teach me.
Go on.
Daddy says music is a bad thing.
And I must stay away from it.
Have you met Rahul?
I've been teaching him since he was ten.
He's blind.
But he's got wings.
Always remember,
feeling something is more important
than merely seeing something.
That's what music teaches us.
I'll take your leave now.
Tarun is waiting for me.
-Where are you going?
-For basketball practice.
So early in the morning?
Well, there's a tournament.
John, how many times should I call you?
Hey, John is very busy.
-Good morning.
-Good morning, Pops.
-"Aberrant"? What's that?
-It's a band from Shillong, Pop.
You know Imti, right?
Who's Imti?
Tell me one thing, Pops.
Why must you always pick on me?
Lona is here. Jay is here.
Lona has been practicing
piano all morning.
And your friend, Jay…
he has gone to the jazz club.
Do you know that?
And what are you doing? Oversleeping!
Jay has gone to Red Mascara?
Where else would he go?
You go back to sleep!
This is my father's collection.
Gershwin, Miller, Peterson.
The secrets of many jazz
greats are hidden here.
You can drop in…
anytime you want.
Why just one song?
Compose a hundred songs.
What's the key?
E-Flat major.
Reharmonize it. Opening in E-flat,
1625 in B-flat.
Now, what can you add to it?
C-7 flat 9.
-F minor?
-Seven.
-B-flat?
-Or?
-Flat 9.
So, play the octaves by
the end full spread chords,
double the melody with your left hand.
G-flat diminished, E diminished.
B-flat with an F in the bass or F minor 7?
Tritone substitute B7 with a…
A sharp…
nine?
Now, that's how you turn on a woman.
Play it!
I'm listening.
Don't you know about Jay?
He's fully engrossed in music.
Sophia, please don't cry.
You should come here.
Come here on Sunday.
If you come here,
you can meet Humpy.
And it will be a big surprise for Jay.
Just come here.
-Everything will be fine.
-Polo!
Okay, Sophia.
I'll call you back in sometime.
Pops, where's the drum key?
It's in the blue box.
How are you?
Are you mad at me?
That was one week ago.
I just don't care anymore.
By the way, Sophia misses you a lot.
I miss her too.
Is that why you're
not answering her calls?
Don't you know I've been busy?
Sure, you've been busy…
with Sheila.
-What are you trying to say?
-Look.
I don't know the ways of the world,
but it's clear as day.
Here's another thing…
Well, forget it.
It is only for you
That my heart beats
But your heart
Now beats for someone else
Darling! Come back to me!
Let's not dwell
On the mistakes we've made
Let's forget the wounds of the past
Come, let's walk together again
Grasping the hand of the wind
Won't you tell me
How deep your love is?
Do you really love me?
If you lie
I'll put a bullet through your heart
Tell me that you love me
Do you really love me?
If you lie
I'll put a bullet through your heart
I'll destroy you
Where did all your love go, my friend?
What about all the promises you made?
Tonight, you are here, my friend!
Where did all your love go, my friend?
Amazing!
Wow!
You're a young sage, bro!
You seem to be practicing a lot!
That was just my anger…
but yours was sheer talent.
You've become a jazz drummer now.
Sure! A jazz drummer!
-What happened?
-It hurts.
Come on, man!
What happened?
Where are you going?
Polo!
Hi!
Janice.
Jay.
What?
Show it to him.
You're getting married?
What an amazing performance, man!
-What a gig!
-Really? What a surprise!
-Awesome!
-Where were you guys?
Another one bites the dust, bro!
Hey! I'm so happy for you.
Come on! Group hug, guys!
Hey! Strike a pose.
Where's Sheila?
I think we're gonna
head to Janice's house.
And if it gets late,
-I'll be meeting you later.
-Hey, Polo!
I'll call you back.
-Polo!
-Hey!
When did you come to Shillong?
You didn't come to see us, man.
Everyone was asking about you.
-How's it going?
-Same old stuff, man.
Puff!
Same old.
Let's have a party.
It's been quite some time.
Wait. We'll go.
I'm telling you, don't be late for dinner.
Please be there on time.
Do you understand? Come early.
-Please. Bring Polo along.
-Okay.
-Okay? Bye.
-Yeah.
Polo!
What are you doing here?
-I was looking for you.
-Me?
-Really?
-Yes.
Isn't this where you hang out?
So, you're getting married!
Come on, man!
-Miss you, bro.
-Same here.
Hey!
Did you check them?
Come here.
-Come here!
-What's wrong, sir?
What is this?
Put your hands up.
What have you got there?
-It's my wallet, sir.
-Turn around.
Check him.
Hey, you! Come here!
Come here quickly!
Put your hands up.
What's this?
It's a phone, sir.
Move it!
Come on, move it!
Keep walking!
Go!
Keep walking.
We didn't find anything, sir.
Sir!
Do you want the drugs back?
You need the drugs?
Do you?
Take him away!
-Idiot!
-Move it!
-Hey!
-Polo!
Move!
Hey!
Bring him here.
Do you know him?
-No, sir.
-What about him?
He's an old friend, sir.
-Friend?
-Yes, sir.
These rogues are your friends?
Go.
Get going!
Miss Sheila.
Hey!
The police were here for a raid.
Really?
The party got canceled.
Everyone has left.
Hey, do you want to…
stay for coffee?
In such situations…
coffee doesn't really mean coffee.
No.
I really need some coffee.
I need to sober up.
So that you can drink again?
Exactly!
Sir! Excuse me, sir!
We've been here for two hours!
Let us go home, please!
Hey, honey.
Something unexpected has happened.
I want you to sit down.
Take her bag inside.
Sit down, dear.
Take a deep breath.
Chandi, where are you?
Who's at the club?
I want to know where Jay is!
He isn't answering my calls!
Hey, come here!
Your name is Polo, right?
Do you know
what happened to your friend?
I hate it when I'm right
about everything that's wrong.
Well…
Arun.
I hate to be the one to say…
"I told you so."
Life is all about…
distances and separations settling in.
And they often lead to…
horrible mistakes!
Do you want one more?
Hey!
Is he conscious?
No, sir. He has taken drugs.
Do you want more?
Do you want more drugs?
Hey!
Music is a religion in Shillong.
And it has no place for people like you.
There used to be some magic…
between us.
But now…
only silence remains.
Methamphetamine.
Do you know what that is?
Do you know what crystal meth is?
There was so much crystal meth
in your friend's blood.
Forget driving, he shouldn't
have been let out of the house.
-Still, he was out with Sheila.
-Jay isn't like that.
He's clean.
So, is this report wrong?
How did crystal meth get into his blood?
Because of me.
-Hey, Polo!
-Dude!
Let's party tonight.
-There's a party going on.
-You call this a party?
You're getting married, man!
I'm talking about acid.
I have even got MD.
I've also got a surprise for you.
-Hey!
-Do you remember me?
-Do you know him?
-No, sir.
This is Shillong, Polo!
Hey! Come on, guys!
Polo!
Turn around.
Hey, do you want to…
stay for coffee?
Chandi, where are you?
I want to know where Jay is!
He isn't answering my calls!
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
You poisoned your close friend!
Do you even know the effects
of such a high dose?
Psychosis.
Seizures.
Brain hemorrhage.
I cannot save your friend.
Please… please, sir.
There's only one option.
We could declare that…
he is an addict.
He'll be sent to rehab.
There, he'd have to serve the full term
and undergo treatment as well.
Rehab is better than jail.
I will send a lawyer.
I hope you can afford him.
I really can't believe
that you're Khagen's son.
We treat all kinds of addicts here.
Get room no. 208 ready.
The patient is on his way.
We understand very well…
addiction is not merely substance abuse.
It's an illness.
Fill up this visitors' form.
You'll get a date to see him.
The canteen closes at 7:30 p.m. sharp.
No sleeping on the premises.
Why me?
Why? What have I done?
What have I done?
Why is this happening to me? Why?
Why me?
What have I done?
I didn't ask for this
I didn't wish to endure this!
Why am I going through this ordeal?
What am I paying the price for?
There's a volcano in my heart
There's a volcano in my eyes
There's a volcano within me
Why did you make it erupt, love?
Love has turned her head.
Keep an eye on her.
Got it.
I am not myself anymore
This isn't who I used to be
Without him
The skies are Grey
Why doesn't the wind lie to me?
Whatever happened to the truth?
Is change really inevitable?
Does this have to end in tears?
Will I burn to ashes in your fire?
What will transpire?
There's a volcano in my heart
There's a volcano in my eyes
There's a volcano within me
Why did you make it erupt, love?
Oh, volcano!
Where are you?
The Grey skies make me numb
What has my life come to?
All my tears have dried up
There's a void in me
Hold me in a warm embrace
And fix me up
Oh, volcano!
There's a volcano in my heart
There's a volcano in my eyes
There's a volcano within me
Why did you make it erupt, love?
I know everything.
I've been watching you.
When a wedding procession
goes by, you run to the window.
When you hear a flute seller's
tune, you run to the window.
You slyly listen to
our neighbors chanting prayers.
How many times have I told you?
You got a beating last time, remember?
Did you like that?
It hurts me as well.
So, why do you still do such things?
Music has ruined our family.
It's taken everything from us.
Don't make the same mistake I made.
Stay away from it.
Understood?
Do you promise?
I canceled my wedding.
I had no idea things would turn so bad.
I know it was all my fault.
No.
It's not your fault. It's mine.
I was warned…
by my father.
But…
I deceived him.
I learned music without his knowledge.
And look where music has got me!
It's an addiction.
I told you, music is an addiction.
Now, look…
Look what that addiction as done to me.
I'm being treated now.
Perhaps I wasn't made for music.
Hey!
-Look at me.
-Dad was right.
Look at me.
Please… don't say such things.
I've spoken to all the judges.
The band members have
given good testimonies for you.
Everything will be fine.
Everybody has a desire in life.
For some, desire becomes
the purpose of their lives.
But for the others,
those desires remain desires forever.
People must turn their desires
into goals and achieve it.
There used to be a saint.
They say, he fell in
love with a courtesan.
But the courtesan spurned him.
She said to him, "Why live in
the confined cage of desires?
If you wish to,
you can fly in the open skies.
You can reach the highest peaks
that we were born to touch."
He wept profusely.
He put his eyes out.
And his love turned into devotion.
It turned into a thousand
songs and poems.
PRIDE
He now lives in the hearts
of millions of people.
The path of truth
is strewn with obstacles.
But no matter how hard the journey is,
we must be persistent and walk the path.
The ones who live a complete life
wouldn't need another birth.
There's a light within us,
and we must awaken it.
That light must be shared
with the other lamps
which are turned off.
You ought to share the light
to brighten up others' lives.
The path of truth will always be hard.
But still, only the path of truth
will help us accomplish our goals in life.
Sophie!
You're welcome!
Oh, volcano!
Where are you
My world has turned upside down
What has my life come to?
Today…
I feel like screaming at death.
Death!
It is so close to me.
Now, only death can…
heal all my wounds.
How is it possible?
This is not my Jay.
He threw it all away.
His dreams.
His goals.
His songs.
My songs.
Everything.
There was nothing left in him.
Not even life.
You have a very interesting story.
You were in search of a hundred songs,
but you slipped into an abyss.
But you're lucky…
you still have those songs within you.
I'm empty from within.
A song…
can never be separated from its creator.
Music has greater strength…
than words and thoughts.
Music is the last bit of magic…
left in this world.
You should believe in it.
I've waited many years for this moment.
That's your mother.
Yes, she's your mother.
O Lord of supreme beauty!
O revered Sai!
Your mother had a divine voice
which could mesmerize everyone.
Would you become the light of my life?
Your father fell in love
the moment he heard her sing.
Look at my pitiable state
I bow down to You, O Lord
O revered Sai!
But your father was already engaged…
to his boss' daughter.
O Lord of divine beauty!
Wouldn't You come to me?
Would You become the light of my life?
Would you become
The language of love, O Lord
O my dear Sai!
O Sai!
I long for a glimpse of You
O Lord of Shirdi
He is the rhythm of my pulse
O Sai!
Would You comfort my yearning soul?
O Lord of Shirdi
The Lord of this timid soul
When your father's fiancee
found out that he loved someone else,
she could not bear it.
Their wedding was called off.
O my dear Sai!
You are the symphony of my soul
You mean the world to me
You are my guide
O revered Sai!
Your blessing is all I need
You are a sea of divine ecstasy, Sai!
While your mother's success
was scaling new heights…
your father's business was collapsing.
I long for a glimpse of You
O Lord of Shirdi
You are the rhythm of my pulse
O Lord of divine beauty!
Wouldn't You come to me?
She sings so well.
Would You become the light of my life?
Bestow me with Your blessings
As days passed,
resentment slowly grew
in your father's heart.
O Sai!
I long for a glimpse of You
O Lord of Shirdi
You are the rhythm of my pulse
O Sai!
What shortcomings of mine
Hold me from your divine gaze?
O Sai!
Would Your grace be upon me?
Congratulations, brother!
This is great news!
She needs to rest.
No more shows from now on.
He forbade her from singing.
O Lord of Shirdi
My dear Lord
Of divine love
You look lovely. Stay well.
Brother!
We got a call from the President's office.
They've invited her to sing.
What do you think?
Tell them she won't make it.
-But--
-You shouldn't even have asked me this.
Soon enough,
he started imposing
more restrictions on her.
He forbade her from singing.
He was under the illusion
that music is the cause of his ruins.
That became his belief.
Your mother eventually gave up singing.
But sometimes, she'd sing to you…
hoping that the tune would
reach you inside the womb.
May you sound like Lord Krishna's flute
With the belief that it will be
etched in your heart and mind.
You are my prayer that has been answered
You are the blessing
I have yearned for
You are my beloved song
-Under the blue skies
-Your eyes shine
-In the depths of the ocean
You don't care about me, right?
I asked only one thing from you!
Why?
How dare you sing!
I forbade you from singing, right?
There will be no singing in this house!
It must stop right now!
There will be no more music!
Don't you dare sing ever again!
You will never sing again!
As soon as you were born,
your father banished me.
But I had promised your mother
that I'd always watch over you.
Come what may.
Look at this.
You can still see her fingers
playing a tune.
You have your mother's eyes.
It feels as though she's here…
in front of me.
Is everything in order?
So, what now?
There's a tune in my mind.
Can I finish it?
Now?
Here?
And of course, standing with them across
the border, across the Line of Control.
That's really the first point.
The second point is…
-Sir.
-I have to give something to him.
He's on air.
Sir, your name?
Just give this to him.
-Whom should I say it is from?
-An old friend.
- Hey, Mahesh!
- Yes, sir?
Where did this come from?
-Someone left it here, sir.
-Who did?
He said he was an old friend of yours.
And welcome to "Roll with…
Ricky!"
We play India's superhit songs for you
right here.
But today's different.
An envelope with a pen drive
was dropped at my studio this morning.
It had only one song on it.
We don't know the composer's name.
We don't know who has written it.
There was just one song.
So, listeners!
Get ready to get your minds blown away!
In a world with thousands of rainbows
Your eyes search for darkness
The fragrance of flowers
Is widespread in the world
Turn up the volume.
Yet your love is on a temporary fence
That holds a flower
For your heart to shine bright
You have to let inside
The divine light
All they sent was a pen drive
with one song on it.
Everyone's hooked on this song.
It belongs to someone anonymous.
Oh, noise! Turn to silence
Oh, deception! Turn into goodness
Oh, greed! Turn into charity
Oh, nothingness!
Fill up the void in my life
For your heart to shine bright
You have to let inside
The divine light
They have just recorded
the song and sent it over.
But no one knows whose it is
or where it's from.
Cut off a tree's branch
And yet, it will give you flowers
Step over a boat
And yet, it holds you safe
Beat the drum
And yet, it gives you music
That's just how pure a mother's love is
For your heart to shine bright
You have to let inside
The divine light
Let your heart shine bright
And just as it shines brighter
Humanity will drink up its light
As far back as he could remember…
his mind had been haunted by a tune.
Your mother eventually gave up singing.
But sometimes, she'd sing to you…
hoping that the tune would
reach you inside the womb.
Oh, Mother!
To lay on your lap is all I want!
You are my ultimate blessing
You gave me everything
You are always there by my side
You will live within me forever
Shower your blessings on me
My life belongs to you
My soul is a part of you
Oh, mother!
How will I ever repay you?
In a world with thousands of rainbows
Your eyes search for darkness
The fragrance of flowers
Is widespread in the world
Yet your love is on a temporary fence
That holds a flower
For your heart to shine bright
You have to let inside
The divine light
For your heart
To shine bright
You have to let inside
The divine light
Mr. Prabhakar.
Ready when you are.
This morning,
Chief Minister Ashwath Prabhakar
posted a link online
with the names of many
eminent personalities.
The names of those who are involved in
corruption and illegal weapon businesses
have been made public.
The list includes 115 MLAs,
CMs of five states,
and oil company directors.
Their contracts and emails
have also been posted online.
The corruption of the politicians
is out in the open.
I should have died in that car crash.
But even death spurned me.
Just that one song kept
playing in my head.
Money and authority…
are these the only things that matter?
A song?
That song has changed me.
And only a song can do that.
That's why countries
have a national anthem,
not a national speech.
Only music with sheer purity
has the power to move you.
What have you done, Prabhakar!
Music either reflects
reality or it doesn't.
Your music is good.
It will also reflect reality someday.
Did this song have that reality?
It showed me the reality.
It changed my whole world.
And now, news from India.
A song at the heart of a revolution.
An eminent politician in India
has done something remarkable
by turning whistle blower
-after a near-death experience.
-Chief Minister…
Ashwath Prabhakar in the union.
A song was being played
on the radio during the protest,
which is considered
to be the reason for change.
A song by an anonymous composer
has brought a change in the world.
He craved neither applause nor fame.
He wasn't filled with self-love.
Nor was he proud of having
written a hundred songs.
There was just one thing
that he wanted.
He wanted to return home.
Because his true home…
was music!
And in music,
he'd be protected forever.
As far as he could remember,
he was haunted by a tune.
An untouched…
unspoken light…
that tore through
all the darkness.